Mhm, I see...Is that so? That's bad news
Got it, I'll see what I can do
Professor, what happened?
Ah, Kakeru, right now monkeys are rampaging all over,
it seems like they're trying to take over the world
Yea, I saw on the news that some towns have
already been completely taken over by the monkeys
We're fighting back against the monkeys,
but Piposarus aren't like regular monkeys,
we're the only ones who can catch them
Yea, they might look dumb, but they're
quick and unexpectedly sharp too
I agree. Also, I just got a call for help,
Please head into town and rescue your
friends trapped by the attacking monkeys
That's bad, we should hurry and go save them!
Who are we rescuing?
Ah, well actually it's...
Toro and friends from Doko Demo Issyo
City life’s pretty
rough, nya~!