This is NSB Emergency News
Since TV stations in many countries have been attacked by monkeys,
and broadcasting is now impossible from those countries,
we're sending you multilingual updates from still available TV stations.
Here is the most recent news.
Enormous air battleships are being spotted all over the world
as the attack of the monkeys continues.
Not only do they continue to take over the capitals of the world,
but they are also appearing at famous banana farms.
So far, they have stolen more than 300,000 tons of bananas
and carried them away with the battleships.
Analysts assume that these stolen bananas
are provided to monkeys in the front line,
that they're high in nutrition, and very much loved by the monkeys.
There have also been many incidents reported
of banana peels discarded by the battleships,
causing multiple residents to slip and fall.
The police are asking you to watch your step when you walk on streets.
We continue with the next news.
43 nations and the local communities have now
organized the Anti-Monkeys World Defense.
Until now it has been difficult to formulate a
counterattack due to a lack of global communications.
A spokesman for the defense has said
effective attacks are going to be possible with these united forces.
Next up,
there has been a report that at one of the local areas,
the monkeys have successfully been forced out.
It is as yet unknown if it was an attack
by the Anti-Monkeys World Defense,
or the result of a local effort,
but the damaged trailer that was driven
by the monkeys was left at the site,
and a laser beam cannon has been found as well.
Stop, you can't film here.
Specialists are saying that the system of this laser beam cannon
cannot be clarified by our current science,
and they believe it is a weapon with substantial power.
There are reports saying that monkeys are building a base
which may deploy the same kind of laser beam cannon
near an industrial complex by the coast.
Military specialists say that to lose this site to the monkeys
would be critical in a struggle to defend earth.
This is not simply monkeying around,
it is an intelligently coordinated offensive
which is causing grave concern to local residents.
I am Fraya DeVapes,
that was the latest news.