This is NSB Emergency News.
The monkey's base the near industrial complex
that we reported on previously
has been destroyed by an unknown force.
Since it has been difficult to get close to this base
due to the monkey's tight security
we have as yet to discover how
and by whom the base has been destroyed.
The Anti-Monkeys World Defence has not a reached a conclusion
either as to what has happened there,
and is currently investigating the situation.
In other news, the monkeys are continuing to build
banana fields for their food supply.
As you can see, more and more areas are being transformed
into banana fields.
In this way, the monkeys are preparing for a future increase
increase in their numbers.
There seems to be nothing we can do about it.
We now have a live report from Moscow.
Migel
This is Red Square in Moscow.
Behind me there are monkeys planting
bananas all over the square
A total of 600 banana trees have been planted so far.
Are you okay, Migel? Migel?
We move on now to a live report on from the front line
protected by the Anti-Monkeys World Defense.
Uh, right now we are on
the battlefield at the Port of Yokohama.
This area has been contested by the monkeys,
and a fierce gunfight has broken out.
Captain, captain, how is the battle going?
Well, even though they're just monkeys, they've been hard to deal with
We've been constantly pushing only to retreat later.
Hurry! Take cover!
It's dangerous! Get down! Get Down!
Is this...a banana?
Idiot! Throw it away! Throw it away now!
That's a banana grenade!
…they're just monkeys, but so hard to deal with…
Captain! Are you okay?! Stay with me!
Are you okay captain?!
Nonaka-san? Nonaka-san?
It appears to be a critical situation at the battlefront.
This just in.
The Anti-Monkeys World Defense has commented
that they are engaged in a severe contact situation with the
monkey's battleships over the cities of Los Angeles, Berlin,
and Paris.
The image you're seeing right now is from Los Angeles.
A local who witnessed the battle says that
the attack by the humans seemed to have no effect on the monkeys.
From what I see, there's no way with all the banana, banana, banana.
Definitely, the monkeys will win the battle.
Back to Japan.
Around the same time that the base at the industrial complex
was destroyed, a huge new battleship appeared
above the nearby stadium.
This battleship is believed to be the one of which the monkeys'
leader Specter was when he first arrived.
Some specialists say that the battleship is providing resources
to the monkeys in order to construct another base.
As this battleship has not been seen since the initial attack,
it's reappearance is causing tension to mount in Japan.
I am Fraya DeVapes,
that was the latest news.