You made it this far too? Quite impressive.
Quit it already, Specter! You're causing trouble for everyone!
Jeez...
Have you not figured out what's going on yet?
You're all so slow...
Haven't you noticed the monkeys are acting a little differently this time?
Huh? What do you mean?
Now that you mention it, it does feel different from before...
True, until now everything's seemed
like the usual monkey behavior.
What are you talking about!
I always have a sense of humor!
Right, I never forget about humor, even in battle.
A good sense of humor is essential for world domination.
Wow, that's deep, I'm kind of impressed.
Eh? What does he mean?
Jeez, what are you talking about?
That's right, enough of this nonsense!
You guys came to defeat me, right?
Then lets get started.
The guy I crushed before
you got here was too weak.
It wasn't even a warm up,
but I think you guys can entertain me a little, right?
What!?
Don’t tell me… You’re not talking about Haruka-chan, right?
Let's go!