W-what!? They've escaped?
You...!
You're useless!
This is bad! We need to get out of here!
Damn it... My plan has been ruined!
This ship is going to explode.
I need to buy some time.
I’ll spread this—
Hm? What's wrong?
You!
What do you think you’re doing!?
Good evening
This is NSB Emergency News
Breaking news
We have been able to obtain
the following document
Under The Monkey
With The Monkey
Flyers like these
are being distributed all over the world
The Anti-Monkeys World Defense
has released the following comment
to the entire human race
Citizens!
Please do not get deceived by these monkeys
The monkeys plan to destroy the Earth,
enslave the human race,
and conquer us!
Do not get deceived!
Local residents are forming their own civilian forces
aside from the Anti-Monkeys World Defense
Here is a report on one of the groups
These villagers are training to capture monkeys
using homemade nets
We're not worried about the monkeys,
we need to teach them a lesson
Meanwhile, these men are making a monkey trap
This is my invention.
It is a trap for catching monkeys.
After placing the banana here...
We wish the best for them
Next, on the news
One of the huge battleships in Japan has crashed into the sea
Details are not yet known
At the scene, we have Mis ato Nonaka
The battleship seems to have crashed into the sea up ahead.
We have someone who witnessed the crash
What was the situation like?
Rather than attacking,
it looks like it self-destructed and crashed.
That’s how it seemed to me.
This footage of the battleship was taken by an eye witness
As the ship explodes and crashes into the sea,
a green, mist-like smoke can be seen coming from it
Since the battleship fell,
there has been a completely new lifeform
vandalizing the cities
These creatures have never been seen on the Earth before,
and very little is known about these creatures at present
We warn you not to go out,
and to exercise extreme caution
I am Fraya DeVapes,
that was the latest news