W-what!? They've escaped?
You...!
You're useless!
Damn! You guys, let's get out of here!
Damn it... My plan has been ruined!
This ship is going to explode.
I need to buy some time.
I’ll spread this—
Hm? What's wrong?
You!
What do you think you’re doing!?
Good evening.
This is NSB Emergency News.
Breaking news.
We have been able to obtain
the following document.
Under The Monkey,
With The Monkey.
Flyers like these
are being distributed all over the world.
The Anti-Monkeys World Defense
has released the following comment
to the entire human race.
Citizens!
Please do not get deceived by these monkeys!
The monkeys plan to destroy the Earth,
enslave the human race,
and conquer us!
Do not get deceived!
Local residents are forming their own civilian forces
aside from the Anti-Monkeys World Defense.
Here is a report on one of the groups.
These villagers are training to capture monkeys
using homemade nets.
We're not worried about the monkeys,
we need to teach them a lesson.
Meanwhile, these men are making a monkey trap.
This is my invention.
It is a trap for catching monkeys.
After placing the banana here...
We wish the best for them.
Next, on the news.
One of the huge battleships in Japan has crashed into the sea.
Details are not yet known.
At the scene, we have Misato Nonaka.
The battleship seems to have crashed into the sea up ahead.
We have someone who witnessed the crash,
What was the situation like?
Rather than attacking,
it looks like it self-destructed and crashed.
That’s how it seemed to me.
This footage of the battleship was taken by an eyewitness.
As the ship explodes and crashes into the sea,
a green, mist-like smoke can be seen coming from it.
Since the battleship fell,
there has been a completely new lifeform
vandalizing the cities.
These creatures have never been seen on the Earth before,
and very little is known about these creatures at present.
We warn you not to go out,
and to exercise extreme caution.
I am Fraya DeVapes,
that was the latest news.