Haruka!
What are you doing here?
Um...
There's something I'm a bit worried about,
so I was investigating the old monkey base...
Haruka-chan, you shouldn’t come to a dangerous place like this alone!
I know...but I...
I really needed to come here!
Ow...
You hurt your leg
I'll treat it
Sorry...
I was careless...
Haruka, what are your plans from here?
I need to gather parts and data
from the three towers in this base
Then let's go together
It's too dangerous to go alone
Eh?
Thank you!
Okay...This should be good for now
Don’t worry, Haruka
Kakeru will be your personal guard
Wha?
M-Me?
W-Why can't you do it Natsumi?
Why do you look embarrassed?
But...but...
Quiet everyone! It’s dangerous here!
Enemies are closing in, we're being surrounded!
Yes, let's hurry
Everyone, stay focused!
We'll infiltrate the base while protecting Haruka!
Alright!