Can you hear me?
It's Haruka!
The monkey's trailer is heading your way,
but it's being attacked...
Please, protect that trailer!
Huh? I don't really get what's going on,
but it sounds like an emergency!
Um, who's on that trailer?
Um... I think you’ve met them before...
They're the Pipotrons
What!?
Why are the Pipotrons driving the monkeys' trailer?
Why does Haruka want to help the Pipotrons...?
Jeez!
You're so annoying with all your questions!
You're always like this!
I'm sure you have a reason right Haruka?
(Kakeru) Huh!? Don't treat me like a kid!
(Natsumi) You are a child!
I trust you
(Kakeru) I'm asking because I don't understand!
(Natsumi) Just like a child!
After all, I don't think the Pipotrons are a bad bunch
(Kakeru) I wouldn't be asking if I understood!
(Natsumi) Ahh, you're really annoying!
(Kakeru) Stop yelling!
(Natsumi) Stop yelling!
(Kakeru) What!? I'm not yelling!
(Natsumi) What!? I'm not yelling!
Everyone! Listen to me!
No matter how many Blobs you defeat,
they'll just keep regenerating!
In order to defeat the Blobs,
you'll need to use a special weapon developed by that man
The trailer being driven by the Pipotrons
is carrying those weapons
I beg you! Please protect the Pipotrons!