Can you hear me?
Hm? You’re that girl from the industrial complex...
The monkey's trailer is heading your way,
but it's being attacked...
Please, protect that trailer!
What's up all of a sudden!?
Also, how dare you order me around like that!
Are any of my subordinates in that trailer?
Um... I think you’ve met them before...
They're the Pipotrons
What!? The Pipotrons!?
Why would I rescue those weird monkeys
from who knows where!?
Listen to me!
Y-Yes...
No matter how many Blobs you defeat,
they'll just keep regenerating!
In order to defeat the Blobs,
you'll need to use a special weapon developed by that man
The trailer being driven by the Pipotrons
is carrying those weapons
I beg you! Please protect the Pipotrons!