Good morning.
This is NSB Emergency News.
First in the news.
People who have decided to join forces
with the monkeys have been sighted in the cities.
They have pleged their allegiance to the monkeys,
and there has been a festive mood all over the world
as these people increase in numbers.
Government of the monkeys,
by the monkeys,
and for the monkeys!
Hurah for the monkeys!
It appears that the situation is quite chaotic.
Next, from Japan.
The mysterious creatures that have been vandalizing the cities,
are thought to be from the huge crashed battleship in the ocean.
We have a helicopter report from the site.
Nonaka-san?
Yes, we're currently flying over the battleship crash site.
It's about 5km from the coast.
The battleship didn't sink,
it's currently floating on the ocean surface.
You can see broken parts scattered around.
It looks like a green gas or liquid is leaking from it.
That green substance might be
the cause of the mysterious creature outbreak.
It's too dangerous to get any closer,
but it looks like a giant creature is moving around inside
Well it seems we're having some technical difficulties.
We will get back to you later with more news.
I am Fraya DeVapes,
that was the latest news.